VLADIMIR GRIGORYAN

Location: Yerevan, Armenia

Phone: 094009277, 096288099

Skype ID: vlad060988 Date of birth: 06/09/1988

Mail: <u>vladimir.grigoryan.1988@gmail.com</u> GitHub: <u>https://github.com/vlad-grigoryan</u>

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/vladimir-grigoryan-b40009b5

PROFILE SUMMARY:

Hello! I am Vladimir Grigoryan, Senior JavaScript Developer.

I have 5 years of experience in web development industry. I have experience in leading teams of Front-end developers in agile methodology, experience in working with multiple development teams. I possess advanced knowledge in the area of web applications. I am apt to strong problem-solving skills, have analytical and investigative mentality, organizational skills, ability to work quickly but with strong attention to details, excellent interpersonal skills in order to meet routinely with individuals at all the levels of the organization as well as outside vendors. Undoubtedly, I own the ability to thrive in a fast-paced production deadline-driven environment.

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS:

Instigate Design Engineering Company (2013 Feb – 2013 May)

Linux Architecture (TCL, BASH)

Web technologies (Html, CSS, JavaScript)

Parallel System Development (Proximus)

State Engineering University of Armenia, Goris, Branch, RA (2005 – 2011)

Informatics & Mathematics

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Ronte Limited LLC

Front End Team lead: November 2018 - Present Remotely (Berlin, Germany)

Tech Flow Studio LLC

Tech lead: February 2018 - November 2018 Remotely (Moscow, Russia)

DataOwl LLC

Full stack JavaScript developer: September 2017 - February 2018 Office (Yerevan, Armenia)

SecurityTrails LLC

Front-end developer: November 2016 - September 2017 Remotely (Los Angeles, USA)

Simply Technologies LLC

Front-end developer: November 2015 - November 2016 Office (Yerevan, Armenia)

Iguan Systems LLC

Front-end developer: March 2015 - November 2015 Office (Yerevan, Armenia)

Instigate Design LLC

Front-end developer: January 2014 - March 2015 Office (Yerevan, Armenia)

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- JavaScript, HTML 5, CSS 3, PUG, EJS, RXJS, jQuery
- Node.js, Express.js, Sails.js, React.js, Redux, Vue.js, Vuex, Angular.js
- NPM, GULP, GRUNT, BOWER, XML, Google API, Webpack
- · Ionic, React native, Cordova
- TCL, BASH and other scripting languages
- C/C++

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS:

- 2004 third place in Mathematics (Armenia, regional)
- 2004 first place in Informatics (Armenia, regional)
- 2002 second place in Mathematics (Armenia, regional)

PROJECTS:

BLACKCATCARD

- Environment: Angular 2+, RXJS, Ionic 3, Typescript
- Duration: 19 months
- Description: Online backing mobile app.
- Role: Worked as Team Lead in Ronte Limited LLC.

BLACKCATCARD WEB APP

- Environment: Angular 2+, RXJS, Ionic 4, Typescript
- Duration: 19 months
- Description: Online backing web app.
- Role: Worked as Team Lead in Ronte Limited LLC.

BACKEND FOR CRYPTO MODULE

- Environment: NodeJS, ExpressJS, mongo
- Duration: 6 months
- Description: Server side for crypto module.
- Role: Worked as NodeJS developer in Ronte Limited LLC.

PETSHARING

- Environment: React native, Redux
- Duration: 10 months
- Description: Pet services app.
- Role: Worked as react native developer in Tech Flow Studio LLC.

PETSHARING ADMIN

- Environment: React, Redux
- Duration: 5 months
- Description: Admin panel for pet services app.
- Role: Worked as react developer in Tech Flow Studio LLC.

BACKEND FOR PETSHARING APP

- Environment: NodeJS, ExpressJS, graphQL, PostgreSQL, Prisma
- Duration: 10 months
- Description: Server side for PetSharing app.
- Role: Worked as NodeJS developer in Tech Flow Studio LLC.

DATAOWL

- Environment: AngularJS, SCSS, HTML5, D3.js
- Duration: 4 months
- Description: CRM application.
- Role: Worked as senior Front-end developer in DataOwl LLC.

SYNC TOOL

- Environment: React, Redux, React-router, ElectronJS, NodeJS, PostgreSQL
- Duration: 5 months
- Description: Data synchronization tool.
- Role: Worked as senior Front-end developer in DataOwl LLC.

SECURITYTRAILS

- Environment: React, Redux, SCSS, Server-side rendering
- Duration: 11 months
- Description: Digital marketing assistant.
- Role: Worked as senior React developer in SecurityTrails LLC.

LATE-FOR-WORK

- Environment: Express.js, Node.js, React.js, Redux, mongo, Amazon S3, Slack API.
- Duration: 2 months
- Description: Automate send the mails 'late for work'.
- Role: Worked as full stack developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

EVENT-BOT

- Environment: Express.js, Vue.js, Vuex, Node.js, mongo DB, FB API, wit.ai.
- Duration: a month
- Description: Facebook Messenger chat bot for wide variety of events.
- Role: Worked as full stack developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

REST-BOT

- Environment: Express.js, Node.js, mongo DB, FB API, wit.ai.
- Duration: a month
- Description: Facebook Messenger chat bot for restaurants, cafes, bars & pubs.
- Role: Worked as back-end developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

SALON-BOT

- Environment: Express.js, Vue.js, Vuex, Node.js, mongo DB, FB API, wit.ai.
- Duration: a month
- Description: Facebook Messenger chat bot for salon booking.
- Role: Worked as full stack developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

BOT-ASSIGNER

- Environment: Express.js, Vue.js, Vuex, Node.js, mongo DB, FB API, wit.ai.
- Duration: a month
- Description: For assign FB pages to bots and add additional info to page.
- Role: Worked as full stack developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

MASSMEDIA

- Environment: Node.js, Express.js, JQUERY, mongo DB.
- Duration: 3 months
- Description: TimeLine for Karabakh war archive.
- Role: Worked as full stack developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

RADFRAME

- Environment: Angular.js, D3.js, Django, Docker, PostgreSQL
- Duration: 7 months
- Description: Australian roadmap generator web application.
- Role: Worked as angular.js developer in Simply Technologies LLC. The project contains six large modules. I refector all modules as John Papa conding style and add new features.

WEBINARIGNITION

- Environment: Angular.js, Sails.js, Node.js, Mongo DB, YouTube API, Socket IO, FB API, Google Hangout API.
- Duration: 4 months
- Description: Web platform for creating professional live & automated webinar funnels.
- Role: Worked as full stack developer in Simply Technologies LLC.

HACKERDECROISSANCE

- Environment: jQuery, Xenforo CMS
- Duration: 3 months
- Description: Forum Growth Hacking and Web marketing.
- Role and Responsibilities: Worked as Xenforo developer in a large team.

EMOCIONDAY

- Environment: Magento 1.9
- Duration: a month
- Description: Web Site on Magento
- Role and Responsibilities: Worked as Magento developer in a large team.

MAGENTO_AUDIT

- Environment: PHP, Apache, MySQL, jQuery
- Duration: a month
- Description: Creating tool which is make audit all general aspects of Magento website.
- Role and Responsibilities: Worked as Full Stack developer individually.

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS:

React express Boilerplate

- Environment: React, redux, redux-sagas, express, NodeJS, mongo
- https://github.com/codeep/React-Express-Boilerplate

React re-captcha google

- Environment: React, google captcha
- https://github.com/codeep/react-recaptcha-google

React re-captcha v3

- Environment: React, google captcha
- https://github.com/codeep/react-recaptcha-v3

CODE EXAMPLES:

Post lists:

- Environment: React, Redux, axios, typescript
- https://github.com/vlad-grigoryan/react-demo-app

Goal App:

- · Environment: React native, Redux, typescript
- https://github.com/vlad-grigoryan/GoalApp

Resize Event:

- Environment: Angular2+,
- https://stackblitz.com/edit/vim8-2-resize-template-41ukzc

Tabs template:

- Environment: Angular2+,
- https://stackblitz.com/edit/vim8-1-tabs-template-gsrvzr